bank-codes.com 2016-12-06

# Privacy Policy

## Our Commitment To Privacy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this Privacy Policy notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our home page and at every point where personally identifiably information may be requested. 

This Privacy Policy was last updated on June 4, 2013. Please check this Privacy Policy periodically, as we may modify it occasionally. 

## The Information We Collect:

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the www.bank-codes.com website. By visiting the www.bank-codes.com website, you accept the practices outlined in this Privacy Policy. 

When you visit the www.bank-codes.com web site, we automatically collect basic information including the address of your internet service provider, the web page that directed you to our site, your web browser software and the pages you visited while on the www.bank-codes.com website. 

On some pages, you can submit ideas, make comments and requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are your Name and Email Address. 

Any ideas you may submit, including text, photo and video become the property of www.bank-codes.com. Please read carefully the Terms and Conditions prior to submitting your ideas. 

## Cookies and Web Beacons

www.bank-codes.com does use cookies to store information about visitors' preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize web page content based on visitors' browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser. 

## Log Files

Like many other websites, www.bank-codes.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track users' movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. 

## The Way We Use Information

We use non-identifying and aggregate information (non-personal) to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals. 

We only use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties. 

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. 

## Third Party Advertising

We also use third party advertisements on www.bank-codes.com in order to financially support the site. Some of these ads might make use of tools such as web beacons and cookies that could potentially also send these advertisers certain information like the web browser you are using to visit the site, whether you have flash installed on your system, your IP (internet protocol), or your ISP (Internet Service Provider). Personally identifiable information data, like name, address, email, phone number or similar are NOT included. 

## DoubleClick DART Cookie

  * * Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to www.bank-codes.com.
  * * Google's use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to our users based on their visit to www.bank-codes.com and/or other sites on the Internet.
  * * Users may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting the [ads preference manager](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/).

You can also opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies for interest based advertising by visiting [aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/). 

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include Google AdSense and Amazon associates. 

## Affiliate Links - Advertising Disclosure

If you purchase a product or service linked from this site, we may receive an "affiliate commission". We are disclosing this in accordance with the Federal Trade Commission's 16 CFR, Part 255: "Guides Concerning the Use of Endorsements and Testimonials in Advertising" and also in accordance to amazon associates programme operating agreement. 

## Amazon

The owner of this website is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to amazon.com. 

## Our Commitment to Data Security

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

## Our commitment to Children’s Privacy

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important to us. We do not require that children submit any personally identifiable information to use our website, play games or access special features. 

If children submit ideas via email, we ask for only the child’s first name (or nickname) and city, in order to identify contest winners. We will only use the email address provided to respond to the child’s submission. It will not be used for any other purpose or sold or distributed to third parties. For videos and photos submitted, please do not show the child’s face or provide any other identifying information. 

## How You Can Correct Your Information

You can correct factual errors in any personally identifiable information by sending us a request that clearly and credibly shows error. 

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. 

## Links to Third Party Websites

We have included links on this site for your use and reference. We are not responsible for the privacy policies on these websites. You should be aware that the privacy policies of these sites might differ from our own.

## Changes to this Privacy Statement

The contents of this statement may be altered at any time, at our discretion. If you have any questions regarding the privacy policy of www.bank-codes.com then you may contact us by: 

## How to Contact Us

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please contact us at via email at info@bank-codes.com or contact us via our contact form: [www.bank-codes.com/contact-us](http://www.bank-codes.com/contact-us)
